const m1c1t3= [
{
question: "What is the purpose of a constructor in Java?",
answers: [
"1. To create an object of a class",
"2. To initialize the instance variables of a class",
"3. To define the behavior of a class",
"4. To declare a variable in a class"
],
correct: [1],
type: "single",
uid: 0,
img: false
},
{
question: "Which keyword is used to create an object in Java?",
answers: ["1. object", "2. new", "3. create", "4. instance"],
correct: [1],
type: "single",
uid: 1,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the output of the following code?\n\njava\nint x = 5;\nSystem.out.println(x++);\n",
answers: ["1. 5", "2. 6", "3. 4", "4. Error"],
correct: [0],
type: "single",
uid: 2,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the correct way to declare a variable in Java?",
answers: [
"1. var x = 5;",
"2. int x = 5;",
"3. variable x = 5;",
"4. int = 5;"
],
correct: [1],
type: "single",
uid: 3,
img: false
},
{
question: "Which data type is used to store a single character in Java?",
answers: ["1. char", "2. string", "3. character", "4. letter"],
correct: [0],
type: "single",
uid: 4,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the output of the following code?\n\njava\nString str = \"Hello, World!\";\nSystem.out.println(str.length());\n",
answers: ["1. 12", "2. 13", "3. 11", "4. Error"],
correct: [2],
type: "single",
uid: 5,
img: false
},
{
question: "Which keyword is used to define a method in Java?",
answers: ["1. function", "2. method", "3. define", "4. void"],
correct: [1],
type: "single",
uid: 6,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the purpose of the 'public' access modifier in Java?",
answers: [
"1. It allows access to the method or variable from anywhere",
"2. It restricts access to the method or variable within the same class",
"3. It allows access to the method or variable within the same package",
"4. It allows access to the method or variable within subclasses"
],
correct: [0],
type: "single",
uid: 7,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the output of the following code?\n\njava\nint[] numbers = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5};\nSystem.out.println(numbers[2]);\n",
answers: ["1. 1", "2. 2", "3. 3", "4. 4"],
correct: [2],
type: "single",
uid: 8,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the correct way to declare a method that does not return any value in Java?",
answers: [
"1. void methodName()",
"2. int methodName()",
"3. methodName()",
"4. String methodName()"
],
correct: [0],
type: "single",
uid: 9,
img: false
},
{
question: "What is the output of the following code?\n\njava\nint x = 10;\nif (x > 5) {\n System.out.println(\"Hello\");\n} else {\n System.out.println(\"World\");\n}\n",
answers: ["1. Hello", "2. World", "3. Hello World", "4. No output"],
correct: [0],
type: "single",
uid: 10,
img: false
}
]




